

DESIGNER / HUMAN

Currently studying Communication Science in Hasanuddin University. I'm a stoic and multidisciplinary designer specializing in creative direction.

Interest in UI/UX design, Front-End Developer, and New Media.

My love for aesthetics, an intuitive message, and achieving challenging goals underpins all of my work.

Adaptive learner. and i work hard to maintai my craft.

Education

SMA IMMIM Putra Makassar 2014-2017

Polimedia Makassar 2017-2018

Graphic Design Studies

Hasanuddin University 2018 - Present

Communication Study

Experience

Freelance Graphic Designer 2018 - Present

Work by any client request for any graphic design service like social media contet, event branding, packging design, logo design, poster, advertising, editorial design (magazine).

Marketing Communication (Intern)

Mar 2020

/ Indosat Sumapa

Learn the flow of marketing strategy of Indosat Ooredo Sumapa by PT. Mitra Distribusi Mandiri. so i know the implementation about ATL & BTL..

Speakers / School of Design BEM-FK Unibos

Jun 2021

2021

Become a speakers in webinar "School of Design". I talk about graphic design fundamental and & practice.

Organization

Secretary / IMMIM Student Council (ISPIM) 2016 - 2017

Vice-Chairman

/ Student Department Association (KOSMIK)

fathurhebak.netlify.app/

+62 821 9193 4374

fathurhebak@gmail.com

Skills

UI Design, Responsive Web Design.

Graphic Design Fundamental (Color, Typography, Layouting), Visual hirearchy, Content Planning, Prototyping, Social Media Ads, Line-art Illustration, Video Editing, Photography.

Tools

Figma, Photoshop, Premiere Pro, Pitch, Google Workspace (Sheet, Docs, Drive)

Programming

- Basic HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- Git

